If you live in England and have a mild infection, don't ask your GP for antibiotics.
如果你住在英格兰，并且有轻微感染，不要让你的家庭医生给你开抗生素。
He will probably refuse and give you something else instead.
他很可能会拒绝，然后给你开别的药。
This is part of a drive to put a stop to harmful infections becoming resistant to these drugs.
这是一项措施的一部分，旨在制止有害感染对这些药物产生耐药性。
Recent figures from the NHS have shown that the number of prescriptions for all types of antibiotics were down by 7.3% on the previous year to about 34 million in 2015 and 2016, which is considered a success by the authorities.
英国国家医疗服务体系最近的数据显示，2015年至2016年，所有类型抗生素的处方数量比上一年下降了7.3%，约为3400万张，这被当局视为一项成功的举措。
Peter Taylor, Professor of Microbiology, UCL School of Pharmacy, says that antibiotics are probably "the safest and most effective drugs ever produced, but they have an Achilles heel - every time we use an antibiotic it alters the levels of bacteria out there in the environment and engenders resistance in a way that is very similar to Darwinian natural selection.
伦敦大学学院药学院的微生物学教授彼得·泰勒表示，抗生素可能是“有史以来最安全、最有效的药物，但它们有一个致命弱点——每次我们使用抗生素时，它都会改变环境中的细菌数量，并以一种与达尔文自然选择非常相似的方式产生耐药性”。
The power of these substances was discovered by Alexander Fleming in 1928 almost by chance.
这些物质的功效是亚历山大·弗莱明在1928年几乎偶然间发现的。
The Scottish bacteriologist returned to his laboratory after a holiday to find a bacteria-free circle around a growth of mould on a Petri dish.
这位苏格兰细菌学家度假归来后，在实验室的培养皿中发现，霉菌周围有一圈没有细菌的区域。
It gave us our first antibiotic: penicillin.
这让我们有了第一种抗生素：青霉素。
The availability of these drugs revolutionised the treatment of infections.
这些药物的出现彻底改变了感染的治疗方式。
In the past STIs spread by bacteria were often incurable and deadly.
过去，由细菌传播的性传播感染往往无法治愈，而且会致命。
Today all it takes to treat them is a trip to the clinic and a course of antibiotics.
如今，治疗这些感染只需去一趟诊所，服用一个疗程的抗生素即可。
Childbirth was very dangerous and routinely ended in death for both mother and baby.
过去，分娩非常危险，常常导致母婴双亡。
Now the risk of a woman dying in England and Wales during labour is between 40 and 50 times lower than 60 years ago.
现在，在英格兰和威尔士，女性在分娩时死亡的风险比60年前降低了40到50倍。
Bacteria will continue to evolve to seek survival and we have to up our game.
细菌将继续进化以谋求生存，我们也必须提升自己的应对能力。
There hasn't been a new class of antibiotics since the 1980s and pharmaceutical companies are looking into a wide-range of alternatives - from compounds from insects to nanotechnology - to develop new weapons in the continuous war against superbugs.
自20世纪80年代以来，就再也没有出现过新一类的抗生素了。制药公司正在研究各种各样的替代方案——从昆虫体内的化合物到纳米技术——以便在与超级细菌的持续斗争中开发出新的“武器”。